https://www.waynepumps.com/privacy-policy

English
Español
Where to Buy
MenuHomeProduct SelectorMulti-Use Pumps – More commonly known as Multi-Purpose or Multi-use Pumps.Electric TransferSubmersible CloseSump Pumps – Automatic pumps used to remove ground water from sump pits.ThermoplasticCast IronBasement Protection SystemsCombination CloseWell Pumps – Used to deliver water from an underground water source to your home.ShallowConvertiblePrecharged Tank Systems CloseLawn Pumps – Used to transfer water from a nearby natural source like a pond, stream or lake.PortablePermanent CloseSewage Pumps – Automatic pumps used when liquid being pumped contains solids up to 2 in. in diameter.Effluent PumpsResidentialSystemsCommercial ClosePool Pumps – Used to remove water from your pool’s cover, and make it easier to open/close your pool.Pool Cover CloseReplacement Parts & AccesoriesDiscontinued Products CloseSolution CenterAbout WAYNEProduct RegistrationBlog / NewsContact Us
Privacy Policy | WAYNE Pumps
/ Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
WAYNE is concerned about privacy on the Web. We have created this Privacy Policy to let you know how WAYNE collects, uses and safeguards the information that is collected and used on the Site. This Privacy Policy works and should be read in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions of Use (the “Terms and Conditions”) but does not modify or supersede them. Terms which are capitalized but not defined herein shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the Terms and Conditions.
WAYNE Collection of Your Information
In the course of using the Site, WAYNE may ask you for your name, e-mail address, postal address, and other information to conduct business with you. WAYNE also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape Navigator, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows ’98 or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink), aggregate data about the number of visits to the Site and/or aggregate data about the pages visited.
How WAYNE Uses the Information
WAYNE uses the non-personally identifiable information (“Aggregate Data”) to improve the design and content of the Site. WAYNE may use the Aggregate Data to analyze Site usage as well as create products and services to fit your needs. Also, WAYNE may share this Aggregate Data with WAYNE’S affiliates and third-party vendors. WAYNE shall own such Aggregate Data and might maintain copies of such as part of its records.
Except as otherwise indicated, WAYNE uses the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you provide: (a) to communicate with you and to assist you with any questions you have about the Site; (b) to cooperate with government officials or parties in litigation under process of law, or as otherwise required by law; (c) to protect the security or integrity of the Site; (d) to protect against a threat to safety or destruction of property; and/or (e) to protect against legal liability. In all cases, however, WAYNE agents, employees and licensors who have access to Personal Information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. WAYNE will not use the Personal Information, except as set forth herein, without your permission; provided, however, WAYNE shall own all such Personal Information and maintain copies of such as part of its records.
WAYNE may use the Personal Information that it collects to offer you other products or services that WAYNE believes may be of interest to you. WAYNE also may make its mailing list available to companies whose products and services might interest you. If you do not wish to receive any such information or to allow WAYNE the right to use your Personal Information as described in this paragraph, please complete the Opt – Out Notice contained in the Privacy Notice below. The Aggregate Data and Personal Information may be transferred, distributed or sold as part of WAYNE or its assets.
If you are a customer of WAYNE, further details about the information we collect and how it may be disclosed is contained in our Privacy Notice below.
Security; No Liability
WAYNE has implemented security measures to help protect against the risk of loss, misuse and alteration of any information under WAYNE’s control. Personal Information provided to WAYNE is encoded using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, a powerful encryption protocol that protects data as it travels over the Internet, provided your browser supports it. Nevertheless, such security measures may not prevent all loss, misuse or alteration of information on the Site, and WAYNE and its third-party licensors are not responsible for any damages or liabilities relating to any such security failures. Furthermore, the Site contains links to other sites, including third party sites. WAYNE is not responsible for nor can WAYNE ensure the privacy practices or content of such other sites.
Cookies
“Cookies” are pieces of data sent from a Web server to a Web browser that enable a Web server to identify users that visit a site hosted by that server. WAYNE may use Cookies in order to identify you to our Site so that WAYNE can provide more customized information and services to you. In general, if you choose, you can identify or disable the use of Cookies by reviewing your browser’s preferences and options; however, the Site will not function correctly if you disable the Cookies.
Modification of Privacy Policy
WAYNE may change this Privacy Policy at any time, consistent with the terms set forth in the Terms and Conditions including by posting the changed or amended Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued viewing of or use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to any such changes or amendments.
How to Contact WAYNE for Any Reason
You may contact WAYNE with questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or anything else related to WAYNE and/or the Site atwww.waynepumps.com or at cs@waynewatersystems.com.
Privacy Notice
——————————————————————————–
Protecting the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information is important to WAYNE.
To help you better understand how your personal information is protected at WAYNE, we are providing you with the following statement of our practices and policies concerning the privacy of customer information. When your account is paid off, charged off or otherwise inactive or closed, we continue to adhere to the policies and practices described in this notice.
How We Protect Your Information
WAYNE maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your nonpublic personal information. We restrict access to nonpublic personal customer information to those associates and third parties who have a business reason to know such information, and we educate our associates about the importance of confidentiality and privacy of customer information.
Information We Collect
WAYNE collects, retains and uses nonpublic personal information about individual customers as permitted by law to provide products and services to our customers. We may collect nonpublic personal information from such sources as:
information you may provide us orally, such as name and address;
information we receive from you on applications and other forms, such as social security number, assets and income;
information we receive from the merchant who sold us your Retail Installment Sales Contract, such as account balance;
information we receive from employment verifications or direct checks with other creditors, such as occupation and payment history;
information we receive from consumer reporting agencies, such as credit history; and
information we obtain in collecting or servicing your current or past accounts, such as changes in your information.
Information We Share With Service Providers and Joint Marketers – No Opt-Out
We may disclose, with no opt-out, the nonpublic personal information that we collect about you as described above to nonaffiliated third parties who provide operational services (process payments, collect past due accounts, process refund checks, etc.), and marketing services (bulk mailing, direct marketing, market research, etc.) for us and to other financial institutions (other lenders, insurance companies, etc.) pursuant to a joint marketing agreement.
Other Circumstances Where We Share Information With Third Parties – No Opt-Out
Other circumstances where we disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties with no opt-out:
To consumer reporting agencies.
In connection with audits or any sale or transfer of your accounts to a WAYNE company or division.
For fraud, security or risk control.
To help complete a transaction you initiate, including information requested to verify the existence or condition of an account.
To resolve disputes or inquiries you may have about your accounts.
With your consent or at your direction, which may be oral, in writing, by telephone, electronic or other means we recognize.
To companies that perform services for us in connection with your accounts, such as data processing and collection agencies.
As otherwise necessary to service your account, or as permitted or required by law.
Information We Share With Affiliated and Nonaffiliated Third Parties for Marketing Purposes – With Opt-Out
We may disclose the nonpublic personal information that we collect about you as described above to affiliated and nonaffiliated financial services companies, such as other lenders, and non financial companies, such as retailers, for their marketing purposes. If you want to opt-out, that is not have WAYNE disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties other than as permitted by law, please complete the Opt-Out Notice below and mail it to us at the following address: WAYNE, 101 Production Drive, Harrison, Oh 45030.
—————————————————————————–
—————————————————————————–
OPT-OUT NOTICE
To opt-out, complete the information below, tear off and mail to: Wayne Water Systems, 101 Production Drive, Harrison, OH 45030
NAME & ADDRESS:     __________________________________________________
TELEPHONE NUMBER: _________________________
SOCIAL SECURITY NO. _________________________
[  ] I do not want my nonpublic personal information shared with nonaffiliated third parties (other than disclosures permitted by law).
1-800-237-0987
WAYNE offers a complete line of pumps that are designed for homeowners, watering gardens, sump and battery backup systems, sewage pumps, pool and lawn. Durable, Reliable and Worry Free.
Our ProductsMulti-Use Pumps
Sump Pumps
Well Pumps
Sewage Pumps
Lawn Pumps
Pool Pumps
Parts & Accessories
Quick LinksProduct Selector
©2017, WAYNE Water Systems, a Scott Fetzer Company. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy | Legal Rights Statement | Terms and Conditions |
CCPA Request
